Okay we are all in readiness to start the match
number four
ye dil maange more Harshal and Saurabh the opening
pair and Prateek Kadam will start
three exciting game and match number four
first ball
sh pitched ball going backfoot and playing at
mid on region for a single
single to start win
for no loss
Saurabh on strike
oh wow good good work by the wicketkeeper
hitting on his body
and that's MSD for you behind the
stumps.
So two fielders on the side as one fielder at
cow corner and one at
sculling
excellent bowling into the block hole straight
to the fielder and mid on very good bowling
from Prateek Kadam
Mr PK
slicing down towards point region it's a very
good throw good fielding
only a single
a different field setup for Saurabh and
different for Harshal that's a good strategy
from Pink Panthers
oh wow good bowling into the block hole chance
direct hit but he was well inside the
crease and
two runs taken there
to leg bye
and this time good strike but the fielder is
there and a quick throw oh confused both the
batsmen yes no yes no and gone that's run out
very good throw by the fielder
and that's a first wicket fall of Adam
Titans
the miscommunication between Saurabh and Harshal
and first wicket fall
good throw from Hemant
one was gone six one Adam Titans
new batsman has come Tejas.  I have booked a ticket for Tejas Express and have come to
bat.  If I win, I will go
home by Tejas Express only.
And this time he has lifted the ball and it has gone very high.   I have
grabbed it.  The ball went so high that it
seemed as if it had come after saying hello to the air hostess.
After saying hello to Aerostus, it is necessary to take the catch here.
Rahul Sawant strikes another wicket.
Second wicket fall for Admit Titans.  It's a
very good judgment by the fielder to take that
catch.  Running and Taken symbol.
Good catch Pratik Kadam
Pratik Kadam steps forward and takes the catch
Nikhil Chauhan the new batter coming at number four
and change in the commentary box the most
experienced OG Baazigar Sir our Mr
Om Singh Sir
who is a great umpire, cricketer, everything, all-
rounder.  He is a good commentator.   Have
joined.  The next voice will be Mr. Om
Singh.  Over to you.
Thanks Mitesh.
For giving me a chance.  I am very
grateful to you.  Next ball from the pavilion.
Rahul
Rahul bowled a fast full toss ball, which
Pratik is a very good fielder, but
here Rahul made a mistake
and
at the end of two overs,
11 runs and two wickets were scored.
Now Pratik Kadam came to bowl with his
second over.   The
power play has ended for the pavilion.  Five players
you can leave out.
And Om Sir C Om Singh Sir see one isle one
team is ready for the photo but no
one has invited us here.  [laughs] The
next ball was a good ball,
wanted to hit it towards point but was completely beaten,
took the inside edge and went into the hands of the keeper, the keeper did
not make any mistake,
our umpires of this match Tajmal Khan and Naushad
sir are very experienced umpires, the
next ball was a very good ball, it was played on the on side, we have to
see the fielder and the fielder made a
little mistake and that is why the score went to the boundary
line for four runs, the
bowler reached 15 runs, Pratik was very angry, the
next ball was
again a full length ball from Pratik.  It was on the feet
as if it was played on the leg side.  Let's see the
batsman run for the second run and
complete the second run also.
Two overs, three balls,
17 runs, two wickets.
Jagan Sir, Karthik Sir and Kannan Sir are the founders of JFSC.
Our Go Live team is
on camera, Bala
and Vinay on broadcaster, the
fifth ball of this over was a little short ball
which was played on the leg side, the fielder
present there can be seen, the batsman ran for a run.  The
second run was risky but
completed.
Very good running between the wickets.
Pratik is very angry with his fielders.
Where one run should have been scored, two runs were scored.
Where there were two runs, four were scored.
Score reached two overs.  Five balls, 20 runs, two
wickets. The
last ball of this over was
also a slightly pitched ball. He could have
played it on the leg side and hit it a little harder
but the ball
and like this he got out on the second run.
Nikhil
looked a bit tired because
Tejas repeatedly made him run for two runs each. At the
end of three overs, 21 runs and three wickets.
Excellent, here Mr. Om Singh
is quite experienced, he has been a cricketer before, he
played season ball, tennis ball very well,
so I would like to say that this is a very
historical ground.  A very
good umpiring for you, you have done a lot of umpiring
here.  What would you like to say about the
upcoming talents who are our emerging faces, who are
called young blood young talents,
what would you like to say about them?  Where
should one start?  Grass root tennis or leather?
No, if you are interested in playing then you should
play with leather ball only because it is taught in that only,
batsman name Sir
Tajmul Sir, batsman name
New batsman Yogesh,
yes I want to tell Mitesh that we will
start with leather ball only, where
[Sangeet] we are taught a lot
and it was a very good catch, he was
standing at extra cover, he had to jump a little,
he made a
good judgement there, he took a good
catch
and you are absolutely right Om Sir that one should
start with leather ball, so we also
started with leather ball, then tennis, then as the
interest increased here, we came to the commentary box.
Very good catch by Vikas, he jumped on time and
hence the catch landed in his hands. Let me
remind you of those good fielders, Cllr
Phillips, legendary fielders, Junty Ras,
Mohammad Kaif, Faf du Plessis, they
played very good cricket, Om Sir, all the
former cricketers have
played excellent cricket.
That era was very different.  Om Sir,
our times were different.  Nowadays,
cricket has become so fast that you cannot miss even one or two balls.
You have to play every ball to score
runs.   Yes, you are
absolutely right.  That was a 50 over game.
He wanted to do five or six overweights.
Rahul Dravid who was a good player.   He
batted well throughout the slog overs.
After 15 overs a power play,
his batting was excellent from 16 overs to 40 overs.  He stood
firm at the crease and kept making runs and the
runs that came in the last 10 overs was a great period, the
ball was very good for India, he should
play towards long on, the player fielding there is
very good fielding, it is
Rahul's second over,
so the three balls have become
very quick, the T20 after 2007,
then now it is a 10 over match, then after five overs
we saw here that there was a three over match,
so the game has become very quick here.
In a moment, tola, in a moment, masha, he would say,
yes Mitesh, you are right.  The game has become so
fast and in tennis we are short on overs.
You
don't get a chance to set 'set hai'.  The next ball is very
high looking bowler pitch but misses it.
Rahul tried hard.
Or at one time it seemed as if he had taken the catch but the
ball did not stick to his hand.  I
would like to say that there must have been Feviquick stuck on his hands.
No, he tried 100%
but is angry with himself.
And Om Sir, it is very difficult to take a reverse catch.  It is
not easy but the
effort he made is commendable.
Next ball from Rahul.   It was a
good ball.  The bowler coming from a good length, the
batsman was completely beaten and the keeper did
his job.
I think he might want to
hit it on the leg side.
Om Sir the batsman should play a big stroke over mid off.
Yes, this ball was above mid-off but the
craze for tennis cricket has increased so much
that 80% of the batsmen play on the leg side only.
They feel that we get more runs on that side.
But nothing like that.
You play according to the ball.  Look, the
ball was played very well at point.
So you must score runs on every ball.
You have to play accordingly.
You are absolutely right.  That is a tactic.
[MUSIC] There's a timing and that
Clever has been our best batter.
God of Cricket Sachin Ramesh Tendulkar.  No matter how
much we praise him, it will be less.
Because he was our Bajirao Singham Sachin
Ramesh Tendulkar.  What a time the 2003
World Cup was, you must be aware Mr. Om
Sir, he played a wonderful innings.   Yes, there is a
very new bowler Vikas and the last
over.  Four overs, 26 runs, four wickets.
Let's see how many runs the batsmen can add in this over.
And Om Sir, you will remember the era of Ricky Ponting, the
era of aggression, Ricky
Ponting used to call Sourav Ganguly aggressive,
but Sir, that team was aggressive and deserved it
too, he did not put anyone in front of him,
till date he was
not at all proud, he had self-respect in
himself, Australia team won 99, 2003,
2007 World Cup back to back, then in 2011
India had a historic victory,
yes Mahendra Singh Dhoni had a
big role in that.  He won the World Cup for India by hitting six runs in the last ball.   Yes.
And they say that Gautam Gambhir's
innings of 97 was a memorable innings.   It was a
memorable innings sir, but the one who
finishes is the one who gets the name.
Gambhir started it and finished it.
MS Dhoni finished it but he took the credit
but Mitesh Sir, at that time the name of
MS Dhoni came up the most because he made us
win but the start given by Gautam Gambhir was
very praiseworthy,
excellent. Gautam Gambhir had scored 75 runs in the 2007 final against
Pakistan,
India had won the match, the
next ball Vikas, the keeper stood a little higher
and
again the ball fell in the no-ball.  The batsman completed one run comfortably.
So Om Sir, how much difference is there in the way the
ball travels in a leather ball.
Here we have to make a strong blow to
hit the shot.
Yes, the ball is a little lighter and softer.
That's why it has to be hit hard.  The
next ball is
played on the off side.
And the batsman completed two runs.
Excellent throw, there was a
fielder present at deep backward square leg.
Four overs, three balls, 31 runs, four wickets.
Om sir, what do you think about the next three balls
?  40 plus [MUSIC] would be a good total.   Should be.  The
batsmen are trying their best but Vikas is also reading the entire ball and
binging the batsmen.  As soon as the
batsman is coming to the off side, they are throwing it further to the off side
and all of them are misshot.
Equal development is not allowing the opposing team to develop.   We are
bowling as per our name and let's
see how many runs the team scores in two overs.   The
next ball was a very good ball.
Hit over the bowler to the off side.   The
batsman ran for one run.  The second run has to be
seen
and he could not complete it
because he was playing a little on the back foot
but that is why he threw this ball a little bit
brilliantly there by Vishram
from long off like the long off
fielder. The throw here was not accurate
but the ball reached the striker's end and he
got the wicket.
Yes Amitesh, the
throw was not as per his fitness
but he got the wicket somewhere. The last ball of
this first innings, 33 for five, will it be 33 for
six, will it be 37 or 39 or 34,
what will you say, last ball Om Sir, I say he
will hit two runs,
two runs, so I am also feeling like that because
Vikas is batting very well,
absolutely right,
he has kept every ball on the off side.   The
batsman is not being given any chance to
hit.   The
last ball of this over is a very good ball
but played towards long on.  There is a fielder behind.
Look and a very good catch, he has taken it
brilliantly.  It is very difficult.
Taking a high catch
and here
Om Sir lost.  Mitesh also lost.  The
fielding team won.
33 for six off five overs, 34 to win.  So
what do you think Om Sir 34 is a good target.
I think the restrictions imposed by Vikas ji will
help
him somewhere.  34 runs will be chased easily.
Yes, the score is not very high but
their bowling is also good.  They will also have to
play well.  Even 33 runs can be defended.
If two good overs come out of that then the
fielding side will come to the field quickly.
Fielding: Fielding team should
arrange the fielding as soon as possible.
And keep your batsman ready sir.
Fielding team, please come in as soon as possible.   There
are many matches.  We have to play 20 matches today.
So I need a little cooperation from you people
also.
I am having an expectation on Orange Juice from my side for the team which will play at the right time.
If the one all one team which is Orange Army wins the first match then there will be an Orange Juice
party and Anirudh ji has said ok
confirmed done, confirmed done email reply has come
fielding team fielding team please
go to the fielding as soon as possible
fielding team
batsman be ready.
So welcome everyone and once again to ICICI
Labord Brokers Premier League 2026 Season 3
Mumbai Edition
and myself Mish Solanki in the com box
joining
umpire of this tournament also joining
in the com box having some chat a little
conversation a little Om Sir previous match
discussions that was a good time
cricketing stories a lot of
you will get to hear here in future so stay tuned
with us.  34 runs needed.  We will have to see who will form the
government.  Everyone is saying that whoever will be the
government.  But we will say that there will be a government of cricket.
Yes Mitesh, you have a lot of experience and a
lot of knowledge.  You call it good commentary.
And your poetry is amazing.
We are waiting for that
opportunity after 12:00.  No,
you will definitely be given a chance.  Please recite some good
poetry in it so that we can be entertained
because we too get
a little bored standing there on the ground.
We will also feel happy after listening to your poetry.
Naushad sir please start a little early.   Yes,
absolutely, he would like to say that flowers bloom
, hearts meet and people like you,
Om Sir, are very difficult to find.
Thanks Mitesh.
So 34 to chase for the Pink Panthers in the coming
five overs.
34 runs needed in five overs.
Dheeraj has come to bowl the first over.  The captain of this team is also from the pavilion side.
Vishram will come on strike and
Pratik Kadam on non-strike end. AKPK will have to be
seen. Pink Panthers, if
more runs come here in the first over.
If the score reaches around 20 runs in the first two overs, then
Om Sir will achieve this target easily. Yes, we have to
see how the start goes. Dheeraj
is also a very renowned bowler. I don't think he will score
10 runs in his over. He is
absolutely the right captain. He will try his best here.
First ball, second innings. Here we go.
Very good ball but he has cut it
towards third man. The ball and this very first
ball goes for four runs. Mitesh
yes, outside edge and this four run ball goes into the gap. I do
n't know, the commentator might be cursing here. Four runs on the
first ball. Strong, brilliant,
explosive four.
Now we need 30 runs in 29 balls. The second
ball of this over was a good ball from Dheeraj. It was a
short ball but he
innovated with a wow scoop shot
and we see this a lot in modern day cricket.
Batsmen like Rishabh Pant, Surya Kumar Yadav, David Warner,
who have innovated,
they seem to be very good. They seem to be the best of today
and safe.  This is his shot, it has
not yet middled the bat, otherwise this too would have
gone for four runs, the ball hit the top edge of the bat, the
next ball was a very good
ball, he
pushed it lightly towards the off side.   The
batsman ran for one run.
I think Pink Panthers will win this match easily
because runs are coming
here and with wide balls and extra
runs the score will increase.
Umpire Mr. Naushad Khan was there
in this over, three balls seven runs, he
wanted to cut the next ball of Dheeraj, there was a very strong appeal but
Naushad did not make any difference, he is a
very experienced and a well known umpire of leather ball and tennis ball.
Tajamul Sir was also
saying that the pair of August T20 has been marked,
yes you must have heard,
like Mahendra Amarnath and Surendra Amarnath in our Indian team,
similarly Tajamul Sir
and Naushad Sir beat them on the next ball, the
keeper did not make any mistake,
these have been very historical players too
like Andy Flower, Grand Flower
from Zimbabwe, Yusuf Pathan, Irfan Pathan,
Hardik Pandya, Krunal Pandya
pushed lightly towards third man, the
batsman ran for one run,
eight runs after one over, no wicket and
26 runs needed in four overs, 26 runs, 24 balls,
Mitesh's score cannot be called easy.  Now
comes Rohit, who bowls very well with the leather ball with his
left arm.   Let's
see his magic in tennis today.  He is
very much needed today.
What do you do here to help your captain win?   Yes,
definitely, we will try to take wickets in this over.
Now Rohit Nambalkar
number seven jersey Rohit for a reason
my bad number seven is not number 87.
Mitesh ji, it seems the power of your glasses is
a little high.
I should definitely change my glasses now.   It was a
very good ball.  It was inserted into the block hole.  The
batsman tried to take a run by pushing gently
but even there the fielder did
good fielding and did not allow him to take the run.
Next ball, Rohit's
fielding changed a bit.
Next ball, Rohit's left round wicket, it was a
very full toss ball, we have to see.
And he made a
slight mistake on a full toss ball and
four runs went into the
super cover area [music]
1.2
balls 12 runs
left round the wicket and this is again
what an innovation wow
absolutely fantastic he has
used his skills well he has scooped
and stand and scoop wow
this shot is a proper start by Dilshan
absolutely right Tilak the
innovation that Dilshan did was by angling down a bit
but the shot he played was
also a no look he did not even see it just
like Rashid Khan in international cricket he plays the no look shot the
most after hitting
he does not even look at the ball to see where it went
but sends it across the boundary line
16 runs no wicket 18 runs needed now
in the coming 33 overs a
bit bad ball here and quite outside off
Rohit bowled a
wimmer and the umpire called no ball
and this ball will be a free hit
or losing a bit of momentum but a
comeback will have to be made now in the coming three balls
this time the ball will be left arm over the wicket from
round right arm left arm round the wicket to
over the wicket
and one  Attempt to hit a shot but it seems
it is a one by
no wide ball, that's wide down the leg side,
we felt the ball was over the stumps, we could
not understand it from this angle but the
umpires have given the right decision.
Yes Mitesh, next
Rohit's left arm over the wicket, this one is also
completely outside off and signals a wide ball.
Umpire Naushad,
yes with this 20 runs have been scored, only 14
runs are needed to win this match.
I think Pink Panthers will win easily.
We were just talking Om sir that 20 runs were scored
in two overs.
No, Mitesh, you are right, 20 runs
and there are still three balls left. The next ball of this over is
hit on the leg side, there is
no player there and this ball will go for four runs.
Yes
and
now Naushad sir is in high spirits. Yes, till now we were
not in high spirits.
24 in
one over, four balls, 24 runs
and 10 runs are needed in just 20 balls.
We were talking about scoring 20 in two overs.
Look, we have scored 24 runs in 10 balls here.
Pink Panthers have
blown it away this time. This ball will go
straight to the tarandal for six runs.
So beautiful, so elegant, so powerful, so
spectacular. Just looking like a wow.
Last ball, last ball.  Dhurandhars batsman Prateek
Kadam
needs four runs in the last ball of this over from
Rohit
which is trending right now Om Sir Dhurandhar, if
you hit Durant before all the players then
double energy comes in the players,
yes
last ball of this over and he hooked it again
and
won the match.  I have made it my name.
Pink Panthers have finished the job in just two overs.
Pink Panthers won the match by
10 wickets.
Absolutely fantastic and the first team
to qualify for the quarter-finals.
Stupendo fantastically fantastically majorly
magical.
Three